Coronavirus is a type of virus.
The one we're all talking about is new and it causes the
disease called COVID-19.
Now most people will only be mildly affected by it,
but it can kill.
It starts by infecting our upper respiratory tracks,
which are the airways from your nose
just above your vocal cords.
You may develop a fever as your immune system starts to fight the virus
and a dry cough.
That's one where you don't produce any slim.
The virus can then spread to the lungs,
making it harder for people to breathe
and it can cause pneumonia.
In the most serious cases,
people can die from the coronavirus.
This is because the immune system can go into overdrive and that
can lead to organ failure.
So we need to do what we can to stop this virus from spreading.
As it gets into your body by breathing it in or through your eyes and mouth,
the best thing to do is wash your
hands regularly and properly for at least 20 seconds.
Catch your colds and sneezes in a tissue and avoid touching your face.