Coronavirus is a type of virus.
The one we're all talking about is new and it causes the disease called COVID-19.
Now most people will only be mildly affected by it,
but it can kill.
It starts by infecting our upper respiratory tracks, which are
the most serious cases,
people can die from the coronavirus.
This is because the immune system can go into overdrive and that can lead to organ failure. So we need to do what we can to stop this virus from spreading.
As it gets into your body, it can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease. It can be a serious disease and that can lead to organ failure.
So we need to do what we can to stop this virus from spreading.
As it gets into your body by breathing it in or through your eyes and mouth,
the best thing to do is wash your hands regularly and properly for at least 20 seconds,
catch your colds and sneezes in a tissue
and avoid touching your face.